Guide to the Arthur Einstein Papers, 1978-2001 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Agency File, 1989-2001 and undated, (19 boxes)
  - McAdams Consumer Healthcare Group (N.Y.), 1994 (Box 24)
  - McCaffrey & McCall (N.Y.), undated (Box 24)
  - McConnaughy Stein Schmidt Brown (Ill.), 1997 (Box 24)
  - McKinney & Silver (N.C.), 1997 (Box 24)
  - Media Direct Partners (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 24)
  - Media First International (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 24)
  - Merkley Newman Harty (N.Y.), 1993-1998 (Box 24)
  - Meyer & Wallis (Wis.), 1994-1998, (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Mezzina/Brown (N.Y.), 1996-1998 (Box 24)
  - Michael Meyers & Associates (Ill.), 1994 (Box 24)
  - Miller/Kadanoff Direct & Interactive (Calif.), 1996 (Box 24)
  - Moffatt/Rosenthal (Ore.), 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - Mother Tongue (Great Britain), 1998 (Box 25)
  - Muse Cordero & Chen (Multicultural marketing--Calif.), 1998 (Box 25)
    [Includes MCC Communique newsletter]
  - Mullen (Mass.), 1992-1998, (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - Napier Partnership (Great Britain), 1993 (Box 25)
  - NCI Masterson (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 25)
  - Nerve (formerly Fuel, Inc.--Ore.), 1998 (Box 25)
  - New York Creatives (N.Y.), 1994-1996 (Box 25)
  - North Castle Partners (Conn.), 1996-2001 (Box 25)
  - Novus Marketing (Minn.), 1996 (Box 25)
  - N.W. Ayer (N.Y.), undated (Box 25)
  - Oasis (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 25)
  - Parrish Wickersham & Partners (Mass.), 1995-1996 (Box 25)
  - Partners & Shevack (N.Y.), 1993-1997, (2 folders) (Box 25)
  - Peak Barr Petralia Biety (Fla.), 1997 (Box 25)
  - Pedone & Partners (N.Y.), 1999 (Box 25)
  - Perich & Partners (Mich.), 1998 (Box 25)
  - Perry Ballard (Mich.), undated (Box 25)
  - Poppe Tyson Interactive (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 25)
  - Posnick & Kolker (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 25)
  - Price/McNabb (N.C.), 1995 (Box 25)
  - Public Sector Solutions (N.Y.), 1994 (Box 25)
  - Ramey Agency (Miss.), 1997 (Box 25)
  - RBT/Strum (N.J.), 1998 (Box 26)
  - R&D/Richards Group (Tex.), 1997 (Box 26)
  - RJ Palmer (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 26)
  - Rockett Burkhead Lewis & Winslow (N.C.), 1994 (Box 26)
  - Rodriguez Communications (Hispanic--Calif.), 1996 (Box 26)
  - Romann & Tannenholz (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 26)
  - Rosner Associates (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 26)
  - Rowland (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 26)
  - RTC Direct (D.C.), 1996 (Box 26)
  - Rubin Postaer & Associates (Calif.), 1997 (Box 26)
  - Ryan Drossman & Partners (N.Y.), 1996-1998 (Box 26)
  - Saatchi & Saatchi (N.Y.), 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box 26)
  - Sard Verbinnen (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 26)
  - Sass & Associates (Md.), 1996 (Box 26)
  - SBC Advertising (Oh.), 1997 (Box 26)
  - Scheyer/SF (Calif.), 1998 (Box 26)
  - Schupp (Mo.), 1995 (Box 26)
  - Seiter & Miller Associates (N.Y.), 1996-1998 (Box 26)
  - Select Communications (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - SFInteractive (Calif.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - SFGT Advertising (Pa.), 1996 (Box 27)
  - Sturm rosenberg King (formerly Sturm Rosenberg Cafferata--Ill.), 1996-1998 (Box 27)
  - S.U.N. (Semper Uetra Numina) Health Care (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 27)
  - Tausche Martin Lonsdorf (Ga.), 1994 (Box 27)
  - TBWA/Chiat/Day (N.Y.), 1997-1998 (Box 27)
  - Telenational Marketing (Neb.), undated (Box 27)
  - Torrenzano Group (N.Y.), undated (Box 27)
  - Tracy-Locke (Tex.), 1991 (Box 27)
  - Transamerica Media Group (Fla.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - Trone Advertising (N.C.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - Upside Magazine (Calif.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - VAMCOM & Partners (N.J.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - Vogt/Wein (Conn.), 1994-1997 (Box 27)
  - Warwick Baker O'Neill (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - W.B. Doner (Mich.), 1995-1997 (Box 27)
  - Welch Nehlen Groome (N.Y.), 1997 (Box 27)
  - West Glen (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 27)
  - West Side Films (N.Y.), 1995 (Box 27)
  - Wickersham Hunt Schwantner (Mass.), 1997-1998 (Box 27)
  - William Cook Agency (Fla.), undated (Box 27)
  - Willliams Worldwide (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - Winward/Cooley (Ariz.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - Witt/Rylander (Calif.), 1996 (Box 27)
  - Woolward & Partners (Calif.), 1990-1993 (Box 27)
  - Wunderman Cato Johnson (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 27)
  - Wurtzel Glenn (N.Y.), 1996 (Box 27)
  - Wyse Advertising (Oh.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - Yaffe & Company (Mich.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - YAR Communications (N.Y.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - Zero Base (Oh.), 1998 (Box 27)
  - Legal Size Files
    - Compaq
      - Ogilvy & Mather (N.Y.), circa 1991 (Box 28)
    - IBM
      - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1993 (Box 28)
      - Press coverage, 1991-1993 (Box 28)
    - New York Stock Exchange
      - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 28)
    - Thomas Weisel Partners
      - Highway One (Calif.), undated (Box 28)
    - General Agency File
      - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1993 (Box 28)
      - Floathe Johnson (Wash.), undated (Box 28)
      - Fox Pavlika & Partners (N.Y.), undated (Box 28)
      - Lowe Lintas & Partners (Calif.), 2000 (Box 28)
      - SHR Perceptual Management (Ariz.), 1996 (Box 28)
  - Three-Dimensional Portfolios
    - Ammirati & Puris (N.Y.), undated (Box 29)
    - Arnold Communications (Mass.), 1996 (Box 29)
    - Campbell Mithun Esty (Minn.), 1994 (Box 29)
    - Campbell Mithun Esty (Minn.), undated (Box 30)
    - Gillespie (N.J.), 1994 (Box 30)
    - Grant/Jacoby (Ill.), 1997 (Box 30)
    - Howard Merrell & Partners (N.C.), 1997 (Box 31)
    - MARC Advertising (Pa.), 1997 (Box 31)
    - McCann-Erickson/A&L (Calif.), 1996 (Box 31)
    - Richards Group (Tex.), 1997 (Box 31)
    - Halbleib/Beggs (Ky.), 1996 (Box 32)
    - Harris Drury Cohen (Fla.), 1995-1998 (Box 32)
    - Martin/Williams (Minn.), 1997 (Box 32)
    - Neiman Group (Pa.), 1997 (Box 32)
    - W.B. Doner (Mich.), 60th anniversary, 1997 (Box 32)
- Lord Einstein O'Neill Partners, 1978-1991 and undated, (4 boxes)
  - Arrowwood meetings, 1978-1989, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Clippings, 1988 (Box 33)
  - Finance, 1988-1989 (Box 33)
  - Forest & Trees (Channel Computing), 1991, (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - General, 1988-1990 (Box 33)
  - IBM, 1988 (Box 33)
  - Legal, 1988-1989, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box 33)
    [Primarily litigation with Lord Geller Federico Einstein/Owl Group]
  - Legal, 1988-1989, (4 of 4 folders) (Box 34)
  - Mead Imaging presentation, 1989 (Box 34)
  - Memoranda, 1988-1991, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Motorola presentation, 1989 (Box 34)
  - New Yorker, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box 34)
  - Profit Sharing, 1988-1989 (Box 34)
  - Saab, 1988-1989, (1-3 of 12 folders) (Box 34)
  - Saab, 1988-1989, (4-12 of 12 folders) (Box 35)
  - Slides, undated (Box 35)
    [Includes Alexander de Markoff, Anne Klein II, Avis, Charles of the Ritz, Chemical Bank, Contel, Dean Witter, Fuji, Hennessy, Loehmann's, Napier, New York Stock Exchange, Prince, Sony, Yves St. Laurent]
  - Staff and client lists, 1988-1990 (Box 36)
  - Success Magazine article on LEOP formation, 1989 (Box 36)
  - Technology Prospecting, 1989 (Box 36)
- Lord Geller Federico Einstein, 1978-1988 and undated, (2 boxes)
  - Finance, 1978-1981, (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - General, 1978-1986 (Box 36)
  - IBM, 1979-1983, (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - JWT and WPP, 1980-1988, (2 folders) (Box 36)
  - Memoranda, 1976-1988, (1-2 of 7 folders) (Box 36)
  - Memoranda, 1976-1988, (3-7 of 7 folders) (Box 37)
  - New Yorker, 1982 July 12 (Box 37)
    [Issue in which LGFE ran advertisements for all 21 client accounts]
  - Porsche discussion, undated (Box 37)
  - Publicity, 1981-1986 (Box 37)
  - Steinway slides, undated (Box 37)
- Oversize Materials, (18 boxes)
  - General Agency File
    - Allen & Gerritsen (Mass.), undated (Box OV1)
    - Anderson & Lembke (N.Y.), 1993-1996 and undated, (4 folders) (Box OV1)
      [Includes SAP America, Dow Plastics, Agfa]
    - Angotti Thomas Hedge (N.Y.), circa 1993 (Box OV2)
      [Includes Saab, Barron's]
    - Barker Campbell Farley & Mansfield (Va.), undated (Box OV2)
    - Berry Brown (Tex.), 2000 (Box OV2)
    - Citigate Corporate Branding (Calif.), 2000 (Box OV2)
    - Citron Haligman Bedecarré (Calif.), circa 1993 (Box OV2)
      [Includes Allure Magazine, Physicians' Formula, KMS, Avia]
    - Cramer-Krasselt (Wis.), 1997 (Box OV2)
      [Accu-Check print campaign]
    - Christopher Thomas Associates (Mass.), 1998 (Box OV2)
      [Ellelte Pendaflex office supplies]
    - D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB) (N.Y.), undated (Box OV2)
    - Doremus (N.Y.), 1997 (Box OV2)
      [Includes Ace Group, ITT Industries]
    - Doyle Inc. (Mass.), 1993 (Box OV2)
    - Draft Worldwide (Ill.), 1999 (Box OV2)
    - Earle Palmer Brown (N.Y.), 1999 (Box OV3)
    - Emmerling Post (N.Y.), 1996 (Box OV3)
    - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1991 (Box OV3)
    - Fifteen Minutes (Calif.), undated (Box OV3)
    - Focus Agency (Tex.), undated (Box OV3)
    - Foote Cone Belding (Calif.), 1996-1997 (Box OV3)
    - Fox Pavlika & Partners (N.Y.), undated (Box OV3)
    - Friedland Jacobs Communications (Calif.), 1997 (Box OV3)
    - Gardner Geary Coll & Young (GGC&Y--Calif.), undated (Box OV4)
    - Glennon Company (Mo.), 1995 (Box OV4)
      [Includes Elk Mountain Ale, Elephant Red beer, Roundup]
    - GMO/Hill Holliday1997 (Box OV4)
      [Includes Charles Schwab, Booz Allen & Hamilton, Accessline, Berenger, webmiles.com, Quantum, fatbrain.com]
    - Goodby Berlin & Silverstein (Calif.), 1991-1993 and undated, (2 folders) (Box OV4)
      [Includes Polaroid, Royal Viking, UNUM, presentation to IBM]
    - Grace & Rothschild (N.Y.), undated (Box OV4)
    - GSD&M (Tex.), 1994 (Box OV4)
      [Includes Fannie Mae, No Fear, Pennzoil, Southwest Airlines, Steel Alliance]
    - Hal Riney (Calif.), 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box OV4)
      [Saturn print and collateral literature]
    - Harris Drury Cohen (Fla.), 1997-1999 (Box OV5)
      [Includes Bombardier NV neighborhood vehicle/Hideaway Yacht Group]
    - Heater Easdon (Mass.), 1994 (Box OV5)
    - Howard Merrell & Partners (N.C.), 1997-1998 (Box OV5)
      [Includes Kimberly-Clark, I-deas.com, MacGregor Tourney golf clubs]
    - Hughes Barry Paschall (Ga.), undated (Box OV5)
    - Kirshenbaum Bond & Partners (N.Y.), 1998 (Box OV5)
    - Lai Venuti (LVL--Calif.), 1995 (Box OV5)
    - Loeffler Ketchum Mountjoy (N.C.), undated (Box OV5)
    - Lowe Fox Pavlika (N.Y.), 1998 (Box OV5)
    - LTS Advertising Services (N.Y.), 1992 (Box OV5)
    - Lunt Sausville Burek (N.Y.), 1997-1998 (Box OV5)
      [Includes Unilever print: Suave, Pond's, Vaseline]
    - Margeotes Fertitta & Partners (N.Y.), undated (Box OV6)
      [Includes Bankers Trust, Putnam Investments print]
    - Marshall Jaccoma Mitchell (N.Y.), undated (Box OV6)
    - Martin Agency (Va.), 1995 (Box OV6)
      [Advertising Age 30th anniversary review]
    - McCann-Erickson/A&L (Calif.), 2000 (Box OV6)
      [Presentation to Thomas Weisel Partners]
    - Merkley Newman Harty (N.Y.), 1997 (Box OV6)
    - Messner Vetere Berger McNamee Schmetterer (N.Y.), 1996 (Box OV6)
      [Includes Volvo print]
    - Meyer & Wallis (Wis.), 1998 (Box OV6)
      [Includes Adventist Health System, Cardinal Stritch University, Econoprint, Marc's Café, Partnership for a Drug Free America, PrimeCare, St. Joseph's Hospital, USXchange print and outdoor]
    - Mojo/FCB (Calif.), 1993-1994 (Box OV6)
      [Includes Adobe, Cheyenne Software, Sun Microsystems, Tandem]
    - Mullen (Mass.), undated (Box OV6)
      [Includes Timberland print]
    - New York Creatives (N.Y.), undated (Box OV6)
    - North Castle Partners (Conn.), undated (Box OV6)
    - Ogilvy & Mather (N.Y.), 1994 (Box OV6)
      [International Paper print]
    - Parish Wickersham (Mass.), undated, (2 folders) (Box OV6)
    - Publicis (N.Y.), 2000 (Box OV7)
    - Romann & Tannenholz (N.Y.), 1995-1997 (Box OV7)
      [Includes presentation to Oppenheimer Fund]
    - Rosenfeld Sirowitz Humphrey & Strauss (N.Y.), 1991 (Box OV7)
      [Includes Bain de Soleil, Royal Caribbean Cruises]
    - Ryan Drossman & Partners (N.Y.), undated (Box OV7)
    - Saatchi & Saatchi (N.Y.), 1995-1997 (Box OV7)
      [Includes Delta Air Lines print]
    - TBWA/Chiat/Day (N.Y.), 1995-1997 (Box OV7)
    - Temerlin McClain (Tex.), 1997 (Box OV7)
      [Includes American Airlines, Nortel, Subaru print]
    - Toolbox (N.Y.), 1997 (Box OV8)
    - Vogt/Wein (Conn.), 1997 (Box OV8)
      [Includes Samsung print]
    - Waylon Ad (Mo.), 1998 (Box OV8)
    - Wieden & Kennedy (Ore.), 1993 (Box OV8)
      [Presentation to IBM]
    - Wieden & Kennedy (Ore.), 1998 and undated, (2 folders) (Box OV9)
      [Includes Microsoft, Nike print]
    - Wong Doody (Wash.), 1998 (Box OV9)
    - Woolward & Partners (Calif.), 1993, (2 folders) (Box OV9)
      [Includes AT&T, Logitech, Oracle, presentation to IBM]
    - Ammirati & Puris (N.Y.), 1989 (Box OV10)
    - Anderson & Lembke (N.Y.), circa 1996 (Box OV10)
      [Materials for NationsBank Montgomery presentation, including Bowne, Business Alliance for a New New York, Energis, and Fore Systems]
    - Angotti Thomas Hedge (N.Y.), 1994, (2 folders) (Box OV10)
      [Includes Barron's, Foster's, Ireland tourism, Lehman Brothers, Saab]
    - Bates USA (N.Y.), circa 1996, (2 folders) (Box OV11)
      [Materials for NationsBank Montgomery presentation, including A.T. Kearney, CoSourcing, EDS, Estee Lauder, Lucky Strike, T. Rowe Price and Westvaco]
    - Bohan Carden & Cherry (Tenn.), undated (Box OV11)
    - Borders Perrin & Norrander (BP&E--Ore.), 1988-1994 (Box OV11)
    - Clarity Coverdale Fury (Minn.), 1998 (Box OV11)
      [Includes Belvedere Vodka, Mid-Minnesota Legal Assistance/Welfare Reform]
    - Cox Group (N.Y.), undated (Box OV11)
    - Crispin Porter Bogusky (Fla.), 1997 (Box OV11)
      [Includes Shimano, Watch Station]
    - D'Arcy Masius Benton & Bowles (DMBB) (N.Y.), 1998 (Box OV12)
      [Includes BankAtlantic, Celebrity Cruises, ProPlayer]
    - DDB Needham (N.Y.), 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box OV12)
      [Includes Bank of New York, Children's Health System, Cigna, Digital, Ductile Iron Pipe, KinderCare, Prescolite, Rickwood, Samsonite, SafeQuest]
    - Fallon McElligott (Minn.), 1998-2000 (Box OV12)
      [Holiday posters]
    - Ferrell Calvillo (N.Y.), 1995 (Box OV12)
      [Includes Wall Street Journal]
    - Friedman & Rose (Mass.), undated (Box OV12)
    - Goodby Silverstein (Calif.), circa 1992 (Box OV12)
      [Includes Dunham Brothers, Finlandia Vodka, Isuzu, Nature Company, New Yorker, Royal Viking Line]
    - Hal Riney (Calif.), 1993 (Box OV12)
      [Saturn outdoor]
    - Harris Drury Cohen (Fla.), 1999-2000 (Box OV12)
      [Includes Sea-Doo/Bombardier, this.com]
    - Hill Holliday (Mass.), undated (Box OV12)
      [Includes Cisco, Micron PC]
    - Kerker & Associates (Minn.), 1997 (Box OV12)
    - Kirshenbaum Bond & Partners (N.Y.), 1996 (Box OV12)
      [Includes Citibank, Neuberger Berman Funds]
    - Martin/Williams (Minn.), 1994 (Box OV13)
      [Includes American Humane Association, First Banks, Grand Groomers, Mariner, Marvin Windows, Shoney's, Target, 3M Leisure Products]
    - Merkley Newman Harty (N.Y.), undated (Box OV13)
      [Includes IBM]
    - Meyer & Wallis (Wis.), 1998 (Box OV13)
      [Includes Dominick's, Shore West]
    - Moffatt/Rosenthal (Ore.), undated (Box OV13)
      [Includes Copper Mountain Trust, Goodwill Industries, KXL-750 Radio, Portland Brewery, Shindaiwa, Warn Industries, Wizards of the Coast]
    - Mojo/FCB (Calif.), 1992-1994 (Box OV13)
      [Includes Adobe, Macromedia, National Semiconductor, Sunsoft/Solaris, Tandem]
    - Mullen (Mass.), 1993-1999, (2 folders) (Box OV13)
      [Includes Agfa, BMW, Campari, Gitano, Money Magazine, Polartec, Reebok/Weebok, Smartfood Popcorn, Swiss Army/Victorinox, Timberland]
    - Rosenfeld Sirowitz Humphrey & Strauss (N.Y.), 1993 (Box OV14)
      [Includes America West Airline]
    - SBC Advertising (Oh.), undated (Box OV14)
    - TBWA/Chiat/Day (N.Y.), 1997 (Box OV14)
      [Includes New York Life]
    - Thomas Weisel Partners, undated (Box OV14)
    - Unidentified agency, undated (Box OV14)
      [Includes D-Day Museum, Oakland Zoo, UNUM]
    - Wells Rich Greene (N.Y.), 1985-1995 (Box OV14)
      [Includes New York Stock Exchange]
    - Woolward & Partners (Calif.), undated (Box OV14)
  - Lord Einstein O'Neill/Lord Geller Federico Einstein
    - Lord Einstein O'Neill clipping books, 1988-1990, (9 folders) (Box OV15)
    - Clippings, 1988-1991 (Box OV16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1992 and undated (Box OV16)
      [Includes LGFE promotional booklet]
    - Laminated advertisements
      - Bass shoes, Birdseye Sodaburst, undated (Box OV16)
      - ConTel, 1983 (Box OV16)
      - Hennessy, IBM, Marie Brizard, 1978-1987 (Box OV16)
      - Saab, 1989 (Box OV16)
    - Print advertisements
      - Data General, IBM, 1987-1990 (Box OV16)
    - Mounted advertisements
      - IBM, 1983-1984 and undated (Box OV17)
      - Saab, 1989 (Box OV17)
      - Steinway, undated (Box OV17)
    - Proofs, Laminated and Mounted Advertisements
      - Channel Computing, 1990 (Box OV18)
      - ConTel, 1987 (Box OV18)
      - Great Northern Nekoosa (GNN), undated (Box OV18)
      - IBM, undated (Box OV18)
      - New York Stock Exchange, 1985-1987 (Box OV18)
      - Saab, 1989 (Box OV18)
      - Steinway and Sons, undated (Box OV18)
    - Miscellaneous oversize folders
      - Print advertisements from unidentified agencies, undated (Box OV18, Folder 1)
        [Includes Acura, Akva Water, Amnesty International, Clarion, Continental Bank, Ikea, Lexus, MacTemps, National Association of Atomic Veterans, Nikon, Shreve Crump & Low, Teva]
      - Goldsmith/Jeffery portfolio, undated (Box OV18, Folder 2)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1990-2001 and undated
  Restrictions on Access: Original audiovisual materials are closed to researchers until use copies can be produced. Contact Research Services staff for further informaation.
  - RL10039-VHS-0001. Accent Marketing, Creative Examples. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0002. Adler Boschetto Peebles Agency TV Commercial Reel. 1996. VHS. Commercials for Primestar, Jimlar, Nashville Network, First Fidelity Bank, CIT Group, Independence Savings Bank, Country Music TV. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0003. ADM Video Productions, Samsung Electronics. Undated. VHS. Simply Samsung Corporate Image, 8:00. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0004. A/L/T/ Agency Reel. 1998 Feb. 10. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0005. Anderson & Lembke TV. Undated. VHS. SAP America, IQNY, PDFA, ILUVNY, Dow Jones, Sharp, Handgun Control PSA, 4:45. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0006. Anderson & Lembke TV. 1998 Feb. 18. VHS. A&L logo; Fore Systems, Corporate, SAP America, IQNY, ILUVNY, Dow Jones, Sharp, Handgun Control, logo, 5:10. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0007. Angotti, Thomas Hedge. Undated. VHS. Saab, Foster's, Fuji, Mony, Barron's, Per Diem, Sunoco, Maalox. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0008. Angotti, Thomas Hedge. VHS. Saab, Irish Tourist Board, Foster's, Mony, Sunoco, Per Diem, Fuji, Maalox, 6:00. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0009. Arian, Lowe & Travis. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0010. Asher & Partners Gala Event. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0011. Asher/Gould Advertising TV Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0012. Austin Kelley Advertising Demo Reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0013. BA Advertising, Award Winning Spots and More. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0014. Backer Spielvogel Bates (BSB) presentation reel. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0015. Balet & Albert Advertising. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0016. Barkley & Evergreen. 1997 June 27. VHS. Well's Blue Bunny commercials, 1:30. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0017. Bates USA Creative Examples. Undated. VHS. Nokia, Benylin, Hyundai, Royal Mail, Verizon, Ad Council Voting, Indianapolis Colts, Pacific Sunwear, Wendy's. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0018. Bates USA HyundaiUndated. VHS. Lou Dobb's Moneyline news article, spots Chair, Speedy. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0019. Bates USA Wendy's. Undated. VHS. Super Value Menu campaign. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0020. Bates USA Wendy's Creative. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0021. BE&P (Barkley Evergreen) Agency Reel. 2001 July 20. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0022. Bernstein-Rein Daring to Think Inside the Box. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0023. Bernstein-Rein Television. Undated. VHS. Bayer, Sprint, Russell Stover, Farmland, Blockbuster, Wal-Mart, Planet Hollywood. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0024. Berry Brown Advertising. Undated. VHS. Friendly's, Daisy, Quaker Rice Cakes, Manwich, Wolf Brand, Quaker Instant Grits, Jimmy Dean, Red Cross. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0025. Berry Brown Advertising. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0026. Biletzki Armoni (Israel) Show Reel. 1994. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0027. Biletzki Armoni (Israel) Show Reel. 1995. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0028. Blattner Brunner/Underwood Reel. Undated. VHS. EDMC, Skybank, UPS, Port Authority, Twist-Mary, Valvoline, CTE, Bronx Zoo, PPG Prostars, BASF, Dreyfus, Gateway Health Plan, Lycos. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0029. Bozell Dallas Creative Reel for Morgan, Anderson & Company. 1991 Sept. 27. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0030. BP&N (Borders Perrin and Norrander) Agency Reel. 1994 Feb. VHS. Washington State Lottery, Portland General Electric, King County Medical, Bowen Scarf Ford/Volvo, Columbia Sportswear, Portland Creative Conference, U.S. Bank. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0031. Brouillard Communications Financial Services Branding. Undated. VHS. GreenPoint Bank commercial, ATM case history, 7:00. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0032. Buntin Group Consumer-Fluent Communications. Undated. VHS. (Box AV1)
  - RL10039-VHS-0033. Associated Advertising Agency/Great Thinking, Don't Wanna Be Reckless!Undated. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0034. Campbell-Ewald Creative Reel. 2001 Mar. 21. VHS. Navy, Pier I, Conoco, ShopKo, Bissell, Privaseek, Onstar. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0035. Campbell-Ewald Recent Work. Undated. VHS. Corvette, Chevy S-10, DIRECTV, OfficeMax, Whirlpool, NFI, Delta Faucet, ACDelco, Chevy Malibu, Asiana. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0036. Campbell-Ewald U.S. Navy Creative Reel. 2001 May 3. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0037. Campbell Mithun Esty. 1996 May 16. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0038. Campbell Mithun Esty Broadcast. Undated. VHS. Andersen, K-Mart, Healthy Choice, Chi-Chi's, Ocean Spray, IBC. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0039. Campbell Mithun Esty Broadcast. 1996 May 16. VHS. IBC, Mannington, PUR, K-Mart. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0040. Campbell Mithun Esty Broadcast. 1994 Nov. 8. VHS. New Business: Andersen case history, ConAgra case history. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0041. Campbell Mithun Esty Broadcast. Undated. VHS. Andersen, Healthy Choice, Target Greatland, GMI/Pop Secret, 3M corporate, Havoline, Borden Creamette, U.S. West, Honeywell, Toro Conclusion. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0042. Campbell Mithun Esty. 1998 Feb. 9. VHS. ConAgra Healthy Choice, 1:00. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0043. Campbell Mithun Esty (CME/KHBB) Agency Reel. 1994 Sept. 14. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0044. Castle Underwood/TBWA Chiat/Day. Undated. VHS. TBWA New York. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0045. Castle Underwood/TBWA Chiat/Day Agency Reel. 1994 Jan. 26. VHS. NYZS, Gant, Dreyfus. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0046. Castle Underwood/TBWA Chiat/Day Creative Reel. Undated. VHS. Wildlife Conservation Society, Gant, Vista Hotel, TV Guide, Dreyfus Corporation, Olivio. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0047. CCP General Demo. Undated. VHS. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0048. Chiat/Day Presentation Reel. 1993 Nov. 5. VHS. Reebok, NYNEX, Neutrogena, Altima, Obsession, Eveready, Home Savings Bank. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0049. Chiat/Day Marty Cook Presentation Reel. 1993 nov. 9. VHS. Reebok, NYNEX, American Express, LaBatt's, First Direct, Nissan Canada. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0050. Citron, Haligman & Bedecarre Agency Reel. 1993 Nov. 3. VHS. Gap, Gallo, Foundation Health, Mirage, Calvin Klein, 6:00. (Box AV2)
  - RL10039-VHS-0051. Clarity Coverdale Fury. 1998 Apr. 21. VHS. Johnsonville Foods Original Bratwurst, 1:00. (Box AV2)